impactfactory.com 2011-05-19

# Impact Factory - Communication training - our privacy policy

##  Privacy policy 

This is the website of Impact Factory. Our postal address is 121 Business Design Centre, 52 Upper Street, Islington, London 

We can be reached via e-mail at enquiries@impactfactory.com or you can reach us by telephone at 020 7226 1877. 

### Data Protection Act 

Impact Factory is registered under the Data Protection Act. 

###  Information collected

Our Web server recognises no personal information. We collect the domain name, but not the e-mail address of visitors to our Web page, and aggregate information on what pages users access or visit. The information we collect is used to improve the content of our site. 

### Cookies

Most areas of our site do not set any cookies. We do use temporary cookies if you book an open course online. This is to store your course choices, providing 'shopping cart' functionality while making your booking. We use PayPal for the paid versions of our Factory Gate articles, and PayPal may use cookies to identify your purchases. This is outside our control. We also display ads from Amazon and Google who may also use cookies to track visitors. This is also beyond our control. 

### Contact

We collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail. If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us an e-mail at the above address, calling us at the above telephone number, or writing to us at the above address, or if you wish to unsubscribe from an email newslettter, by visiting /new.shtml. 

Visitors who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line will only receive telephone contact from us with information directly relevant to their enquiry. If you do not wish to be contacted, please let us know. 

### Third party use

No personal information collected on the site is passed to third party organisations. 

### Future use

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically. 

You may prevent your information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by e-mailing us at the above address, calling us at the above telephone number, writing to us at the above address. 

### Access to your information

Upon request we provide site visitors with access to all information that we maintain about them. You can access this information or have this information corrected by sending us an e-mail at the above address. 

### Security

We do not hold any sensitive information on our site. Financial transactions are dealt with by PayPal, which is responsible for their security. 

### Feedback

If you feel that this site is not following its stated privacy policy, you may contact us at the above addresses or phone number.
